A woman was charged with allegedly violating a Rhode Island City law against feeding
wild animals. A woman was charged with allegedly violating a Rhode Island City law
against feeding wild animals.
The 55 -year -old woman's neighbors blame her for making the area's rat problem
worse. Newly installed cameras captured several rats active in the middle of the
day. The 55 -year -old woman's neighbors blame her for making the area's rat problem
day. Neighbors say that it's even worse during the night.
The woman and her parents, who own the home, told reporters that she's being charged
for feeding birds.
Neighbors say that it's even worse during the night.
The woman and her parents, who own the home, told reporters that she's being charged
for feeding birds.
Neighbors say that it's even worse during the night.
The woman and her parents, who own the told reporters that she's being charged for
feeding birds. Who would have known just loving animals gets you that much trouble,
she said. It is prohibited to feed any wild animals, including birds, in Rhode
Island City. Who would have known just loving animals gets you that much trouble,
Island City. Nevertheless, while the woman's intention was to feed birds, it is
clear that rats were also benefiting.
Nevertheless, while the woman's intention was to feed birds, it is clear that rats
were also benefiting.
Nevertheless, while the woman's intention was to feed birds, is clear that rats were
also benefiting. Antony Moretti, Director.